Bedau, Hugo A.; Papers apap199
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Advocacy Organization, 1958-2003; 3; 10 cubic ft.
  - Other Organizations, 1957-2002; Undated; 3.5
    - Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolition of the Death Penalty, Stockholm, 1977; 3.5.19 (Box 6 (3-Advocacy Organization), Folder 19-21)
      - Death Penalty Reporter -- Newsletter of National College for Criminal Defense (NCCO), University of Houston, 1980 September-1981 April (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 26)
      - Death Penalty Reporter, NCCO, 1981 May-1981 August (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 27)
      - Fellowship of Reconciliation, Fellowship, 2000 May-2000 June (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 28)
      - Hands Off Cain, 1993-1998 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 29)
      - Illinois Committee to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1959 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 30)
      - International Society for Criminology, 1972-1974 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 31)
      - Massachusetts Council for the Abolition of the Death Penalty, 1928 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 32)
      - Massachusetts Death Penalty Representation Committee, 1989 (Box 7 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 33)
      - Moratorium Now/ the Moratorium Campaign, 1998-2002 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 1)
      - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, 1991-1995 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 2)
      - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, 1998-2002 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 3)
      - National Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers The Champion, 1984 March; 1985 November (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 4)
      - National District Attorney's Association, 1965 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 5)
      - New Jersey Council to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1957-1963 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 6)
      - NYCLU, 1972-1974 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 7)
      - New York Lawyers Against the Death Penalty -- Memorandum in Opposition to S.600/A.1070, 1989 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 8)
      - New York State Bar Association, 1989 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 9)
      - New York State Defenders Association The Defender, 1986 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 10)
      - Northeastern Law Library, 1973 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 11)
      - Russell Sage Foundation, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 12)
      - Southern Coalition Report (Newsletter), Published by Southern Prison Ministry, 1976-1990 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 13)
      - The Southern Poverty Law Center, 1976-1977 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 14)
      - The Spangler Report, Newsletter of the Spangler Group-Massachusetts, 1994-March 2000 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 15)
      - The Spangler Report, Newsletter of the Spangler Group-Massachusetts, 2000 August-2001 July (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 16)
      - Supreme Judicial Court Historical Society of Massachusetts, 1993-1996 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 17)
      - Team Defense Project, 1988 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 17A)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1958 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 18)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1961 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 19)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1965-1967 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 20)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1969 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 21)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1973 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 22)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1974-1975 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 23)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1977 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 24)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1980-1985 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 25)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1986-1989 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 26-27)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1990 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 28-29)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1991 (Box 8 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 30-31)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1992 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 1-3)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1993 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 4-6)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1994 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 7-8)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1995 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 9)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1996 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 10-12)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1997 (Box 9 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 13-16)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1998 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 1-4)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 1999 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 5-6)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 2000 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 7-10)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 2000 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 11-12)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 2001 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 13-14)
      - Various Advocacy Organizations, 2002 (Box 10 (3.5.19-Amnesty International, Conference for the Abolitio), Folder 15)
- Subject Files, 1955-2003; 4; 16.79 cubic ft.
  This series contains news clippings, pamphlets, court documents, academic papers, bibliographies, reports, journals articles, and newsletters about capital punishment that Bedau devoted his life towards studying. Some of the material is organized by the name of the defendant in a capital punishment case; some is organized by state or country, and some is organized by subject. This series contains a diverse amount of media formats including VHS and cassette tapes.
  - General Files, 1955-2003; Undated; 4.1
    This subseries contains various material organized alphabetically by subject. Topics include capital punishment as a deterrent, race, innocence and wrongful convictions.
    - Abolishment, 1959; 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Accomplices, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Appeals, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Articles, 1955-1973 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - John Ashcroft, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Capital Punishment, 1959-1962 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Capital Punishment, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Capital Punishment Bibliographies, 1968; 1971; 1987 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Capital Punishment Bibliographies, 1971-1976 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Capital Punishment Bibliographies, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Capital Punishment Bibliographies, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Capital Punishment Cartoons (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Capital Punishment Pamphlets (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
    - Capital Punishment Pamphlets, Opposing Viewpoints, 1974; 1986; 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Capital Punishment Reprints Catalogue, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Capital Punishment Statutes, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Clemency, 1963-1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18-19)
    - Clemency, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Consensual Executions, 1993-1998 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Conservatives for Capital Punishment, 1983-1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Cost of Executions, 1980-1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Council of Europe (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Dangerousness, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Death Penalty Data Sources, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Death Penalty Films, 1970-1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Death Penalty Information Packet, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Death Row, 1972-2000 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Death Row Lawyers, 1990-2001 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
    - Death Row Who's Who, 1967-1970 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Death Row Writings, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Delays, 1960 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Deterrence, 1971-1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7-8)
    - Deterrence -- Journal articles, Papers, etc. (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9-11)
    - Drugs, 1988-1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Electrocution, 1976-1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Espionage, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Executions, 1977-1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Execution Costs, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Expedition, 1983-1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Fairness, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Federal Death Penalty, 1986-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
    - Firearms and Murder, 1983-1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Firing Squad, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Gas Chamber, 1992-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Habeas Corpus, 1984-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
    - Homicides, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Inhumane, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Innocence Protection Act, 2002 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Institutional and Parole Conduct, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - International Extradition, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Lou Jones, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Journal Articles (1867/1936), Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Journal Articles, 1950-1969 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Articles (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
      Journal Articles, 1970-1974 / News articles, 1971.
    - Journal Articles, 1971-1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Journal Articles, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
    - Jurors, 1986-1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Juveniles, 1983-2001 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
    - Legislative Research, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Lethal Injection (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
    - Life and Death, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Life Imprisonment, 1983-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Mandatory Capital Punishment Statutes, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15-16)
    - Mandatory Capital Punishment, 1983-1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Mentally Retarded, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Military Death Penalty, 1983-1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Murder Etc, 1977-1998 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Murder of Police Officers, 1976-1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Murder/Suicide, 1973-1981 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Murder Rate, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - National Death Penalty Media Project, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - News Articles Supreme Court, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - News Articles, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - News Articles, 1976-1978 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27-28)
    - News Articles, 1977-1979 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Nixon asks Congress to Restore Death Penalty, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Parliamentary Debates, (Abolition of the Death Penalty) Bill, 1964 December-1965 April (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Parliamentary Debates, (Abolition of the Death Penalty) Bill, 1965 May-1965 August (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Parliamentary Debates, 1965 October; 1973 January (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Physicians, 1990-1997 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Plea Bargains, 1975-1988 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Police and FBI on Capital Punishment, 1960 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Politics and Capital Punishment, 1988-1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Politics, 1990-1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Post Fowler Arguments, 1975-1976 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Post Furman, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Prison Homicide, 1980-1984 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Prosecutors on Capital Punishment, 1972-1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Public Executions England and America, 1763-1800, 1987 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Public Opinion, 1972-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16-20)
    - Race, 1972-1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
    - Race, 1979-1986 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Race, 1988-1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Racial Justice Act, 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Rape, 1972-1975 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Recidivism, 1967-1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Referenda, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Religion, 1959-1962 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Religion, 1990-2001 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Religious Pamphlets, 1955-1964 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Religious Pamphlets, 1970-2000 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Script, "Advocates" Death Penalty TV Show Transcript, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Script, "The Death Penalty" James Lee, 1958 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Script, "In the Valley of the Shadow" Gary McDonald, 1980 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Survey Form, ca. 1960 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Survey Research, 1967-1989 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Terrorism, 1975-2002 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - TV Executions, 1973-1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - United Nations, 1959-1975 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - United Nations, 1973-1983 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Vetoes, 1977-1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Viewing Executions, 1991-1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Violence Theories, 1973-1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Wardens, 1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Women, 1984-1998 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Innocence/Wrongful Convictions, 4.1.116
      - Innocence, 1977 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 1)
      - Innocence, 1981-1983 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 2)
      - Innocence, 1988-1990 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 3)
      - Innocence, 1989-1998 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 4)
      - Innocence, 1990-2002 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 5)
      - Innocence, 1995-1999 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 6)
      - Innocence -- Journal articles, Papers, etc. (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 7-8)
      - Miscarriages of Justice, 1940-1986 (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 9-11)
      - Wrongful Convictions, 19th Century Cases (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 12)
      - Wrongful Convictions, Journal articles, Papers, etc., Undated (Box 6 (4.1.116-Innocence/Wrongful Convictions), Folder 13-22)
  - Case Files, 1957-2002; 4.2
    This subseries contains material related to various capital punishment cases. They are arranged alphabetically. They contain newspaper clippings and court decisions.
    - Mumia Abu-Jamal Case, 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Salvador Agron Case, 1962 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Earnest Aikens Case, 1971 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Alvaro Alcorta Case, 1960 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Timothy Baldwin Case, 1996 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Case, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Elmer Branch Case, 1971 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Charlie Brooks Case, 1982 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Enfrid Brown and William Johnson Case, ca. 1974 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Enfrid Brown, John Clinkscales, and William Johnson Case, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Ted Bundy Case, 1986-1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Central Park Jogger Case, 2002-2003 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Caryl Chessman Case, 1959-1960 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - John Clinkscales and William Johnson Case, ca. 1974 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Paul Crump Case, 1961 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Dawson Five, 1973-1979 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15A)
    - Dickerson Case, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Martin Fitzpatrick Case, 1971-1973 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - James Foster Case, 1960 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - William Furman Case, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Gary Gilmore Case, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Larry Griffin Case, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Ducan Hansen Case, 1960 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Bruno Hauptmann Case, 1982-1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Donnell Johnson Case, 2000 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Sylvester Johnson and Stanley Cassidy Case, 1964 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Donald Ketchel and Thomas Sears Case, 1957 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Edgar Labat Case, 1960 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Richard Lapointe Case, 1992-1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Leopold and Loeb Case, 1963 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Sandra Locket Case, 1978 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - William Maxwell Case, 1967-1969 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Timothy McVeigh Case, 1997-2001 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Billy Moore Case, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Lyman Moore Case, 1971 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Robert O'Neil Case, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Norman Redlich Case, 1963 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Benjamin Reid Case, 1962 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Jose Rodriguez Case, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Ethel and Julius Rosenberg Case, 1968-1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti Case, 1966-1992 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - John Spenkelink Case, 1979-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Stuart Case, 1990-1995 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Walter Wood Case, 1979 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Geographic Files, 1953-2002; 4.3
    This subseries contains material organized alphabetically by place. The first section is material related to the United States, the next is divided by individual state, and the third is about foreign counties.
    - United States, 1958 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - United States, 1959 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - United States, 1960 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - United States, 1961 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - United States, 1962 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - United States, 1963 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - United States, 1964 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - United States, 1965 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - United States, 1966 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - United States, 1967 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - United States, 1968 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - United States, 1969 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - United States, 1970 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - United States, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - United States, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - United States, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
    - United States, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - United States, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - United States, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
    - United States, 1977 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1-3)
    - United States, 1978 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - United States, 1979 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - United States, 1980 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - United States, 1981 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - United States, 1982 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
    - United States, 1983 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - United States, 1984 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - United States, 1985 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - United States, 1986 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - United States, 1987 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - United States, 1988 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - United States, 1989 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - United States, 1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - United States, 1991 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18-19)
    - United States, 1992 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - United States, 1993 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - United States, 1994 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - United States, 1994-1997 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - United States, 1995 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
    - United States, 1996 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7-9)
    - United States, 1997 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10-12)
    - United States, 1998 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13-15)
    - United States, 1999 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
    - United States, 2000 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3-7)
    - United States, 2001 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
    - United States, 2002 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10-11)
    - Alabama, 1983 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Arkansas, 1989 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Arizona, 1985 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)